

Wei-Han Hui (Ambrose)

Email: ambrosehui0105@gmail.com Website: https://lp65082001.github.io

Tel: (+886) 972106451

Physical modeling and ML/DL application. I have a strong academic background in constructing and applying physical models, particularly in the realm of mathematical modeling, simulation tools, and multiscale simulations. I also have extensive experience in machine learning and deep learning applications, with a track record of successful interdisciplinary collaborations, demonstrating excellent communication and problem-solving skills, especially in **protein-related** fields. In short, I am committed to translating theoretical knowledge into practical applications to solve complex real-world problems.

Experience

11/2023 ~

Advanced Algorithm Engineer (Generative AI)

ACCTON, Hsinchu County

- RAG framework pipeline.
- Code Review application.
- Associate robot.
- AWS bedrock, lambda, and API gateway.

09/2019 to 08/2023

Ph.D. project

National Taiwan University, Taipei

- * Physical modeling (protein structure)
 - Temperature effect and crosslink effect in collagen.
 - Conformation of ion channel and ion pathway.
 - Linear polymer model mapping from atomistic model to coarse-grained model with multi-target parameter fitting.
 - Uncovering absorption mechanisms between graphene and small molecule.

*ML/DL application

- Protein function prediction by graph neural network.
- Osteogenesis imperfecta lethality prediction by graph neural network.
- Collagen strain prediction by XGboost.

07/2022 to 12/2022

Deep learning intern (object detection) Industrial Technology Research Institute, Hsinchu County

- Unbalanced object detection.
- Deploy models on the Google Cloud Platform.

Skill Highlights

- Molecular dynamics simulation
 - LAMMPS, NAMD.
- Generative models (methods)
 - VAE, transformer (LLM), stable diffusion.
- ML/DL/RL models (methods)
 - XGBoost, SVM.
 - CNN, YOLO, GNN, CLIP, SAM.
 - GA, CEM.
- ML/DL framework
 - Scikit-learn.
 - Tensorflow (Keras).
 - Pytorch (Geometric).
- Programming language
 - Python, Matlab, C++.

Education

- Ph.D., Artificial Intelligence center of Department of Civil Engineering, National Taiwan University 09/2019-08/2023
- M.S., Department of Civil Engineering, National Taiwan University 09/2017-07/2019
- B.S., Department of Civil Engineering, Chung Yuan Christian University 09/2012-07/2016